http://www.footballcardshop.com/privacy.asp

Most Popular
Dan MarinoJoe MontanaPeyton ManningBrett FavreEmmitt SmithTom BradyBarry Sanders
Cam NewtonJerry RiceTroy AikmanJohn ElwayTim TebowAndrew LuckRobert Griffin
Top Rookies
Joe BurrowTua TagovailoaJalen HurtsJerry JeudyJustin JeffersonJ.K. DobbinsBrandon Aiyuk
Most Purchased
Joe BurrowSaquon BarkleyTom BradyPatrick MahomesTua TagovailoaBaker MayfieldJustin Herbert
Browse Other Sports
(Baseball, Basketball, Golf, etc.)
By Set
Browse All Football Card Sets
Latest Releases
2020 Panini Illusions2020 Panini Phoenix Fire Burst2020 Absolute2020 Panini Mosaic2020 Donruss2020 Elite2020 Prestige2020 Chronicles Draft Picks2020 Panini Legacy2020 Score
By College
Browse Players By College
Most Popular
USCMiamiOhio StateFloridaOklahomaTennesseeMichiganTexasAlabamaLSU
Notre DameSouthern MississippiVirginia TechGeorgiaFlorida StateStanfordPittsburghPenn StateAuburnCalifornia
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.)
is committed to respecting your privacy. We've structured our
websites so that, in general, you can visit FootballCardShop.com
(Nexmark, Inc.) on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing
any personal information. Once you choose to provide us personally
identifiable information (any information by which you can be
identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to
support your customer relationship with FootballCardShop.com
(Nexmark, Inc.).
This statement regarding the privacy of the information you
provide online covers five main areas: Awareness, Choice, Access & Accuracy,
Security, and Oversight.
Awareness
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) provides this Online Privacy Statement
to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices
you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make
this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and other
pages via a hyperlink.
What we collect
On some FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) web pages, you can order products,
make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information
collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information, transaction
information.  PayPal.com will also collect credit card information in
order to process payments on our behalf.
How we use it
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) uses your information to better understand
your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your
information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you,
to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize our web site for
you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not
retained for other purposes.
Who we share it with
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) will not sell, rent,
or lease your personally identifiable information to others.
Choice
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) will not use or share the personally identifiable
information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described
above without letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated,
we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish
to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do
everything we can to honor such requests.
Access & Accuracy
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) strives to keep your personally identifiable
information accurate. We make every effort to provide you with online access
to your registration data so that you may update or correct your information
at. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps
to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make
corrections.
Security
FootballCardShop.com (Nexmark, Inc.) is committed to ensuring the security
of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy,
and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate
physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring
sensitive data such as credit card information.
Oversight
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send them
to this email address: administrator@FootballCardShop.com.
